secp.gov.pk 2015-06-08

# The Official Website of SECP

|   |  |  |  |   
---  
| Privacy Policy  
---  
Securities & Exchange Commission of Pakistan (SECP), in accordance with laws stipulated by the Government of Pakistan and internationally accepted standards, is committed to protecting the privacy of users visiting its website. 

As a policy matter, SECP does not collect information on any user visiting its website, unless the information is voluntarily provided by the user himself. In case of a requirement by any agency within the Government, the information may be shared with them although information will never be given out for commercial purposes without the consent of the user. 

The information collected by SECP can be used for official purposes, internal reviews, and improvement of website and to contact users, if required. Please note that any website hosted within Pakistan, may have to disclose their records on order of courts / Government agencies for the purpose of civil, criminal or administrative matters. Similarly SECP may be required to disclose personal information in response to valid legal orders such as search warrants, subpoena or court orders.   
  
Top  
Information collected by SEC   
All information that can be used to identify an individual is considered "personally identifying information." The SECP does not retain personally identifiable information about user based upon browsing of our Website unless user chooses to provide such information to SECP through sending an e-mail, registering as a user, participating in a survey, responding to a feedback etc.

Securities and Exchange Commission, like other departments, agencies and regulatory bodies, may request personally identifiable information from you in order to provide requested services however, such information is handled as in the case of an in-person visit to that same department, agency or organization.  
  
Top  
E-mail and forms   
If you send us an electronic mail message with a question or comment that contains personally identifying information, or fill out a form that e-mails us information, we will use this personally identifying information only to respond to your request. We may redirect your message to another government agency or person who is in a better position to respond to your query or comment.

All e-mail messages received contain the e-mail addresses of persons who voluntarily communicated with or requested information from us. User's e-mail addresses are not shared with any non-governmental or commercial entities without the user's consent. When a user has given SECP their e-mail address for purposes of communicating with or requesting information from SEC, that communication becomes part of the public record and may be subject to public inspection and copying if not protected by law.

Information submitted via e-mail or web forms may be at risk of being intercepted, read or modified. You are advised not to pass on any personal and confidential information such as security passwords and credit card numbers while using this Website unless specifically required by an authorized person. Securities and Exchange Commission shall not be liable for any misuse or loss of any such information.   
  
Top  
Security Measures   
SEC, considering the importance of integrity of information and systems, has taken appropriate safeguards ensuring the security of information. We strive to rid our systems and data of destruction, corruption, unauthorized access and breach of confidentiality. 

Several steps have been taken to safeguard the integrity of our computer systems and networks. These steps include, but are not limited to individual authentication, the security of transmitted data, security monitoring, auditing and encryption of your information.  
  
Top  
User information sharing  
Except as provided by applicable laws, we do not collect, use or disclose user information without the user's knowledge and approval. We do not share user information with third parties unless we have informed users about the disclosures or have prior consent.   
Links to other Sites.  
Top  
Policy Revision and Notification of Changes   
The Securities & Exchange Commission may at any time revise or update this policy without notice. We may inform our users about policy changes through notices on this page containing a version number and date. Any information collected under the current policy will remain subject to these terms. Information collected after any changes take effect will be subject to the revised privacy policy.  
Top  
Disclaimer  
The SECP Website includes links to websites operated by other government agencies, non-profit organizations and private businesses. When you link to another site, SECP Privacy Policy will not apply, however, you may be subject to the Privacy Policy of that new website, if one exists. The Securities & Exchange Commission of Pakistan is not in any way responsible for the privacy practices or content of external websites.

Providing any linkage to SECP website from another website must be made keeping in view the general standards and corporate image of SECP website. Any site containing unlawful, infringing, defamatory or obscene material or information which provides a link to SECP website may be asked to remove the linkage or to face legal consequences.  
  
Top  
|    
---
